You're early, man.
What'd you do?
Scare all your customers away?
Very funny.
Man, at night, it's off the hook in here.
Well, I'm here.
What's the deal with that picture?
You said, yeah, that's gonna
take a little explaining,
but first check this out: a game.
It's an MMO for the Amu sphere.
It's what replaced nerve
gear on the market.
Huh, so it's a VR MMO just.
like sword art.
Alfheim online?
Uh, actually, it's pronounced Alfheim.
Yeah, it means
land of the fairies.
Fairies, huh?
Let's go to the end of the end of the day.
I can't wait for a miracle.
I'll be able to see you
in the middle of the sky.
I'll be able to see you in the future.
Land of the Fairies.
Sounds like a cute game.
Yeah, that's not what I hear, brother.
For one, PKing's allowed, and it's
got this hardcore skill system.
What do you mean, hardcore?
I mean, the game's not
level-based, it's skill-based.
You gotta use your skills
over and over to improve them,
and combat depends on your
real-life physical abilities.
That is hardcore.
There's no sword skills.
Other than that, it's like SAO with magic.
What I hear, people are going nuts for it.
Because in the game, you feel
like you're flying. Say what?
You know how fairies have wings?
Well, the game's got
this flight engine thing.
And once you figure it out, you can fly.
Whoa.
How's a player controlling?
No idea, man.
I do hear it's a pain
to get used to, though.
Yeah, I bet.
How are you supposed to control
something you don't have?
Maybe you have to use the
muscles in your back. Ahem!
Uh, right.
Okay, getting back to Asuna.
What does she have to do with this game?
Look familiar?
It looks like Asuna.
I kinda figured you'd say that.
Would you cut the crap?
Where the hell is this?
Alfheim Online.
That was taken in the game.
Right in the middle.
you got the world tree.
At the top of that, there's
this legendary castle.
Players are
divided up into nine races.
Each one of those races is trying to
be the first to get to the castle.
Why don't they just fly up to it?
It's already been tried, but
the game's got a limit to how
long you can stay airborne.
Check it out.
These five players stacked up,
bigger players on the
bottom they tried launching
themselves like a rocket
good idea it's insane but
kind of clever yeah well
those cats didn't even make
it past the lowest branch
they did manage to snap
a couple shots though
when they checked out the
pics they saw something
weird a birdcage you could
call it that and after
zooming in on it as far as
they could they saw her okay
but if it's really Asuna,
what's she doing there?
Wrecked progress?
Without getting into specifics,
you could say I'm the one.
keeping Asuna alive.
Hey, Gil.
Can I borrow this for a couple days?
Sure, it's cool.
You thinking about going?
Yeah, I gotta check this out.
A game where it's okay to die
shouldn't be that big a deal.
Crap, I still gotta buy
the hardware for it.
It's compatible with what you got.
The Amu-Sphere is just a NerveGear
rig, but with better security.
That's a relief.
The battle's not over till it's over.
You feel me?
Get a route and come back safe.
Sure.
And when I do, let's all meet up here.
God, what am I doing?
I'm so stupid! Hey, I'm back. Help!
Where'd you go?
Here.
Uh, I, I thought I was gonna die!
You're such a spaz.
Those muffins aren't going anywhere.
Sugu, about last night. Yeah? What?
I just, I don't know.
Thanks a lot.
Thanks to you, Sugu, I feel better.
You're right, I can't give up.
And I'll get Asuna back no matter what.
Well, good luck.
I'm looking forward to getting
the chance to meet her.
When you do, I'm sure you'll hit it off.
Anyway, I'd better get going.
we're having the ceremony here on january
26th a week from now save the date
i need your help again one more time
Blink, start!
Welcome to Alpine Online.
Please enter your gender and the
name you wish to be identified as.
You're THE Kirito?
You're a hero. It's an honor.
There are nine races of
fairies to choose from.
Please select which race
you wish to play as.
That one looks good.
You have selected Spriggan.
Your character's appearance
will be decided at random.
Do you wish to continue?
You will now be Teleport to your
hometown in Spriggan territory.
Good luck, player.
Now what?
What's going on?
Agh!
I'm back in another game.
Even after everything I just went through.
Wait, where am I?
There it is. Thank God.
Okay, where's the status window?
Huh?
What is this?
Oh, please don't be a bug.
It's all my skills and stats from SAO.
The hell's going on?
Am I back inside SAO?
Oh crap!
Come on.
Please be here.
Hey, Yui.
It's me.
You remember?
I do.
I remember you, Daddy.
Yui
Mommy.
You must be hungry.
Now what about breakfast?
Okay.
I
like
it.
Mommy.
Daddy.
Daddy. Daddy.
Daddy!
You're back.
It's a miracle.
So, do you know where you are
or what's going on? Uh-uh.
Oh, well, we're not in SAO anymore.
We're in a totally different game now.
It's called Alfheim Online.
I need a few seconds to assess it.
From what I can tell, this world has been
copied from the Sword Art Online servers.
Really? Yes.
The engine, programming, and
graphics format are exactly the same.
The Cardinal system needs updating, but
that's the only thing that sticks out to me.
Huh.
That makes sense, because Argus
was the company running SAO.
They folded and Wreck took over.
Yeah,
and if Wreck's already got all of Argus'
technology, it figures they ported over.
Although, when I checked I still had
my old skills and stats. Strange.
I'll take a look at your
data and see what I find.
Very interesting.
You're right.
This is the same character data
you used when you were in SAO.
The formatting for saved
data is almost identical.
Whatever skills you had that were similar
in both games were ported over and merged.
Oh, that's why my
dual-wielding skill's gone.
Not just that.
All your items seem to be lost, too.
You might want to delete them before the
error detection program finds out about it.
Yeah, I better.
Okay, what am I going to
do about my skill level?
No one else can see them.
Well, no one except the Game Master, and
as long as he doesn't, you should be okay.
Oh, awesome.
Huh, I guess I'm not a beater anymore.
Just a plain old cheater now.
How are you being
identified by the system?
Let's see.
It's classifying me as a
player support program.
In the world of the game,
I'm a navigation pixie.
Hey!
This is what I look like as a pixie.
Whoa.
No, Daddy, that's annoying.
You had admin privileges in SAO.
Do you still have them?
No,
the system will only
allow me to access the
wide area maps and the reference database.
Oh.
Listen, Yui.
I think your mommy might be stuck
in here somewhere. Mommy? Really?
What do you mean she's stuck?
After SAO was cleared, Asuna
never woke up in the real world.
I found out she was seen in Alfheim.
There's a picture, but
it's too blurry to tell.
What are we going to do?
Well, I got a pretty good
idea where she might be.
It's something called the World Tree.
I think it's over there.
Mommy's there? Really?
Hang on a second.
I was supposed to start the game
in a town in Spriggan territory.
So how come I ended up here
in this forest instead?
I don't know.
Your location data may be corrupted.
Or perhaps there was some interference?
Either way,
it would have been nice if the game dropped
me a little closer to the world tree.
Well, let's go.
Wow, these are my wings, huh?
How do I fly with them?
You have to access your controller first.
Raise your left hand, then position your
fingers like you're grabbing something.
Pull it toward yourself to elevate.
Push it away to descend.
and move it left or right to turn.
Okay.
Hold down the button to accelerate.
To decelerate, just
ease up on it a little.
As long as your wings are
shining, you can stay airborne.
But you can't fly forever.
After a while, you'll
need to rest your wings.
This is great!
I think I've got it down.
Do me a favor, scan the map and
see where the nearest town is.
There's one in Sylph
territory, west of here.
It's a town called Sylvain.
It's the closest one.
Something wrong?
There are other players near here.
Hey, wait up for me!
Weepa!
Hurry it up, Recon.
A little further and we'll
be in Sylph territory.
Watch out, Recon!
Jeez, they never give up.
Okay then.
Prepare for battle!
What are you doing?
Sigurd and the others
are already there by now.
I'll keep these guys busy.
You try to knock one of them down, okay?
If you say so.
Show me how useful you can be.
We can win this!
Idiot! Don't stop!
Hurry!
Recon!
Sorry about this.
We're on a mission, though.
Give up your money and
items, and we'll let you go.
What are you acting like such
a gentleman for, Kagemune?
Yeah, we haven't fought
a chick in forever.
Come on, let's waste her.
Go on, try it, but I'm
taking one of you with me.
Whoever's not afraid of dying,
come on, step up and get some.
You're a stubborn girl.
Suit yourself.
Damn, gotta work on those landings.
What are you doing? Go! Get out of here!
Would someone tell me why three big
guys are fighting one single girl?
That's pretty uncool if you ask me.
What did you say?
Better get your ass out
of here, noob. Fast!
You asked for it.
Get ready to die!
Huh?
See ya.
Excuse me.
Hate to interrupt.
Do you mind if I take care of this?
Uh, I guess if you really want to.
It's not like they were gonna let
you walk out of here alive anyway.
Then sit back and let me at them.
Oh, crap. Where'd he go?
Okay, who's next?
I'm going to raise my hand.
I'm going to say.
I'm going to pray.
I love you.
It's too late for now, I don't have
to answer any questions or questions.
Next time, Captive Queen.